Kris Klingberg

Github.com/mygithub Linkedin/in/mylinkedin Twitter/mytwitter

My work experience has been enhanced by using technology to sell solutions in various venues. My current role requires more in-depth use of technology. My technical skills are being enhanced through Udacity's development courses.

Technical Skills

Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

Frameworks/Libraries: jQuery, Bootstrap, Knockout.js (MVVM)

Other: Sublime, GitHub, Brackets

Project Experience

Neighborhood Map - qithub.com/frontend-nanodegree-neighborhood-map

In Progress

- Single-page, responsive application built with Knockout.js framework and hosted on GitHub Pages.
- Developed a full-page map that loads with 20 popular jazz clubs in Atlanta, GA
- User can view recent pictures taken at each location (retrieved by AJAX request to Instagram API).

Arcade Game Clone – *github.com/frontend-nanodegree-arcade-game*

September 2015

- Clone of the classic game, Frogger. Udacity provided the art assets and game engine.
- Coded player, enemies, and other game entities in JavaScript's object-oriented pseudo-classical style.
- Created enemy subclasses with different movement patterns and sprites.

$\textbf{Website Optimization} - \underline{\textit{qithub.com/frontend-nanodegree-m}} obile-\textit{profile}$

In Progress

- Optimized critical rendering path of existing website to achieve PageSpeed Insights score above 90.
- Eliminated inefficiencies in the website's scroll animation. Site now scrolls at 60 frames per second.

Work Experience

AT&T Corporate Business Solutions - Sales Executive

Atlanta, GA | January 2015 - Present

- Designed marketing material for human resource benefits sites at businesses across all segments
- Collaborated with marketing representatives to ensure issues were resolved before publication
- Consistently submitted material print requests on time while working on multiple projects with different schedules.

AT&T Business Integrated Solutions - Business Account Manager

Atlanta, GA | March 2010 - January 2015

- Designed solutions to integrate with existing systems for small and medium businesses
- Worked in multi-functional team comprised of engineers, application specialists, buyers and suppliers
- Consistently built new business relationships to ensure quotas were met or exceeded

Verizon Wireless - Business Account Executive

Macon, GA | August 2004 - October 2009

- Designed mobility solutions to integrate with existing systems for healthcare and transportation businesses
- Collaborated with solution providers and business partners to ensure final solution met specifications
- Consistently built new business relationships to ensure quotas were met or exceeded

Education

Udacity - *Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree* **Elgin Community College** — Business Management, A.A.

In Progress 1985

Honors and Activities

- AT&T Employee Sponsorship Program GASC *Member*
- AT&T Business Integrated Solutions Leadership Council *Member*
- Macon Chamber of Commerce *Member*

January 2015 - Present

2012-2013

August 2004 - March 2010